Looks like she's not coming this year.
She comes every year.
I'll go get two bowls of soup.
Two of the chef's special.
Tell me what you think!
She might be blind,
but her soups are a real treat!
Where'd he go?
He's alive! He is alive!
What happened to me?
You had some trouble
coming out of the tube.
Right. We all just fought that man,
with his collection of panties.
-Where's Yugo?
-Not here yet.
He got into a fight
with Princess Pain-in-the-Patoot.
I heard that, Elely!
He's the pain in the butt
and he's a selfish little pig!
-Are you talking about our Yugo?
-Do you know any others?
What did he do to get you this worked up?
None of your business!
Not the easiest way to travel.
-You guys make it okay?
-Of course!
-Amalia, can we talk about--
-No, Yugo. We cannot.
Okay.
Have you had any time
to check out this place yet?
So, that's it, then?
You've moved on that quickly?
But I just asked if you wanted
to talk and you didn't want to!
I've never seen you give up so quickly.
So, you do want to talk, then?
I did want to, but not so much now.
But you just said that you...
You don't even know what you want!
I don't know what I want, really!
Stop!
Will you two stop acting like kids?
The only one with a reason
to complain here is Elely.
The poor girl lost her whole family
and we may not find them.
So, your stupid lovers' quarrel...
We are going to find them!
Out of the three,
one or two must have made it.
Papa... He said he was going
to catch up with us soon.
And now... he still hasn't made it here.
I just know something bad
has happened to him.
You'll see.
This isn't your father's first rodeo.
That man keeps dying
and he always comes back to life.
Don't worry about Eva and Flopin.
We'll find them, I promise.
So, there's no time left to lose!
Do these tiles on the floor look familiar?
They look the same as in your house.
You're right. So, we must have reached
the temple of the demigod Enutrof.
I wonder what he looks like.
It seems to have musical protection.
Much more complex than I've ever seen.
But if anyone is the right man
for the job, it's Ruru.
Yeah, well, it would be nice
if Ruru would hurry it up,
instead of making little girls cry.
There, my makeshift rope
should hold up now, Mama.
You impress me more each day, my love.
You're becoming so clever.
I've got a secret for you, Mama.
I don't get it from Papa!
Sweet-talker,
but that's not nice about your dad.
Careful. We don't know what's down there.
This might be our only chance
to get out of here, so we got to do this.
Flo?
I'm okay!
You can come down.
It looks like we made it home, Mama.
My special homemade powder is able
to show us which of these tiles
are used to open the door.
Now I just have to test
all the possible combinations.
How long?
All right, then,
this is going to take forever.
The two of you are seriously pathetic.
Ruel, did you figure it out?
Huh? Yes. No. Maybe...
What do you mean?
Did you do figure it out or not?
Please.
Oh, thank you, sir.
Thank you, kind lady.
Oh, thank you.
Watch it, fleabag!
That coin's mine! It's mine!
-I wasn't trying to steal it.
-You're still a fleabag!
Take a look at yourself!
Fleabag!
Awesome! You see, Amalia?
You always say that Ruel is useless,
but he's come through for us twice.
He does have a real talent
for breaking into strangers' homes.
-You okay, Ruel?
-Huh?
Yeah. It's just that tune
brought back some old memories.
Well, in any case, you did it once again.
Of course I did.
"Did it" is my middle name!
So now it's a labyrinth.
That's just great!
-It's a trap.
-How do you know?
I'm absolutely sure it's a trap.
Papa taught me to trust my instincts.
There are four doors and four of us.
It's not a coincidence, so it's a trap.
Iops don't have the most reliable
instincts, but I see your point.
It would be worse to think they knew
there'd only be four of us now.
No, that's not possible.
In any case, they want to separate us.
But we can easily beat them.
With this magic thread,
we'll stay connected.
We'll each take a door.
The first one to find the exit
tugs on the thread twice.
The others can follow the thread.
That's a great idea!
You're getting a little bit too familiar.
I'm impressed, Amalia.
You'd make an excellent Enutrof.
I'd rather die, Ruru.
Amalia, you are...
Impressive?
Yeah. You impress me, Amalia.
A good start
if you want me to forgive you.
-Okay, let's go!
-Yes, let's get going!
A hallway each.
You think I'm scared!
Where are you going?
All right, that was pretty easy.
I should have known.
Yuk! That smells horrible!
Luckily, I'm used to Flopin's farts.
Thank you! By the way...
Yeah, nice try.
Hey, buddy, your days of freedom
are almost over.
Risdo the Compulsive Chopper,
that's a pretty big catch, for a fleabag!
No begging today?
Never more than once a week,
or people get used to your misery.
The Chopper is a madman.
You won't get him alone.
But I know where he's hiding.
He's still going to kill you.
He's a ferocious beast
who lives to chop things up.
You're going to need help.
Why don't we catch him together
and split the bounty?
But I have vital information.
-I'll give you 30%.
-40%.
35.
Deal!
I just have to tell the others.
I found it near a cemetery.
I hope you like it.
I don't care about the ring, Ruel.
I just want you.
-Let's have a honeymoon.
-You're paying for it.
40%.
Since we've been together,
my savings are drying up so fast.
So are mine, Ruel.
I love you, but I feel bad.
With you, I want to enjoy life,
so I spend all my money.
I feel so guilty.
If we continue on like this,
we'll end up broke.
But I have an idea that might fix things.
Let's take a break.
Just a few years to save up enough
so we'll never have to worry.
We can meet back here every year
for a bowl of soup.
Fortune awaits, my darling!
Arpa... Arpagone.
Hello, Mr. Stroud!
How is my husband doing?
What are you doing here?
You... never came back for me.
Do you remember the last time
we saw each other?
Guess who!
A charming voice, soft hands,
I'd say the most beautiful of women!
What a charmer!
I've ordered. You're paying this year.
Ruel... I don't have a single Kama.
-What?
-My fortune is in your hands.
I can't stand being away from you.
I love you more
than all the gold in the world.
I choose you, Ruel!
But I don't understand.
There's nothing to understand.
If you love me, you'll have to choose
as well. Me or your fortune?
I'm going to need time
to think about this.
-Listen, I... need to go.
-No!
You chose your fortune over your wife.
And what about now?
You're getting old.
Ready to keep your promise?
Ruel! Finally!
Hey... Yugo, why the long face?
Is something bothering you?
I've been thinking about Adamai.
I really want to see him, but I'm also
scared of what he's become.
-And with Amalia?
-Huh?
That... It's really complicated.
There's nothing complicated about love.
I'm not sure if what I feel is love.
I've known Amalia for years.
So, you'd think my biggest problem
is still being a child, but it's not.
I don't feel ready for anything. I feel
like I'm going to live for an eternity.
The only one who can understand is Adamai.
Have you told to Amalia?
Yes and no. I tried to, but I can't ever
seem to get a word in with that princess.
She's so self-absorbed,
she can't see people's distress.
He's got some nerve!
Amalia!
You're crying?
No. It's just some dust in my eye.
Let's go join the others!
It was pretty easy here, right?
Easy as pie, thanks to Amalia.
Sure. Let's move on to whatever's next.
I want to get this over with.
That's what I want to hear!
-Is everything going according to plan?
-As expected, Oropo!
I've got my husband back
and your chameleon has taken his place.
Perfect!
Ruel, it's good to see you again,
my friend.
Don't think you're being punished.
This is my way of thanking you...
for everything.
I'm going to make you into a god!
Think about it, Ruel.
If you take the place of the god Enutrof,
eternity will be finally ours,
eternity
and all of the treasure in the world.
You and I will be the wealthiest
and happiest couple in the Krosmoz.